(Hwang In Youp)
(Lee Hye Ri)
(Baek Sung Chul, Lee Yul Eum)
(Dream To You)
(All people, events, and backgrounds are fictional.)
(This drama includes footage created using AI.)
(Children and animals were filmed under strict safety guidelines.)
Do you think you're a flaw only in my life?
Didn't you know?
That you're the one who ruined her life?
Woo Su Bin, you are my regret.
You should go back to that day too,
and see how I feel.
What's wrong?
This...
Is this because of me?
Tell me.
Who said it was because of you?
Did you ask me to come chasing after you?
- Did you crash into me? - Joo Yi Jae.
Be quiet. Your mother just fell asleep.
Let's talk outside.
(Episode 6)
Were you never going to tell me?
How could I? It was too humiliating.
If you knew how much I liked you, you'd obviously get a huge ego.
Gosh, I'd never want to see that. I can never tell you.
The moment you saw me,
you should've cursed me out or slapped me.
Don't you remember?
I did all of that. I cursed at you and slapped you.
Joo Yi Jae.
Don't talk about it like it's nothing.
This might have just happened for you,
but for me, it's been over ten years.
I spent all that time blaming you.
I guarantee if it weren't for my curse,
you'd be even better off than you are now.
How can you... Even in this situation...
I lived with so much self-pity, and...
it was only after meeting you again that I realised...
I was actually blaming myself.
That I couldn't forgive myself.
I told you.
My regret...
- isn't you. It's me. - But still.
What if I hadn't left?
Then maybe it wouldn't have happened.
But what are you going to do about it?
What? Are you going to turn back time for me?
Or are you going to erase my memories?
I'm going to be sorry.
I'll keep being sorry, regretful, and blaming myself.
This is why I was afraid...
Don't tell me I can't even do that.
It's my burden to bear.
It's not your fault, Su Bin.
It's not your fault.
It's okay.
- You're up already? - You're up?
I'm an early riser. I always wake up at 5am.
You don't have to cook. Please rest, Mom.
I want to do this for you.
I'll leave it ready, so eat whenever you're hungry.
- Where are you going? - I have to go home.
Your father will be waking up soon.
Mom.
I brought your things.
I brought a few outfits for now, so take a look...
and let me know if you need anything else.
Su Bin.
Let's eat, Mom. It's been so long since I've had your cooking.
Is this doenjang stew's smell?
Okay, the one with the sun drawing on it...
is for the morning.
And after lunch...
Since you'll take care of the flowerbed later,
I'll draw a flower here.
Gosh, you're a sharp one.
If I'd known I was going to live this long,
I would've learned how to read.
It's not too late.
I'll be dead soon anyway. What's the point?
You used to say that back when I was a student.
That's right. You're right. I did.
The one with the crescent moon is for the evening.
And for the one you take before bed...
A smiley face.
I love bedtime the most. So draw a big, happy smile.
Okay.
(Take Before Bed As Needed)
I'm going to check on you when I get back from Seoul.
- Make sure you take them. - All right, I will.
If you collapse again,
they said you could seriously injure your back.
I know.
Mom.
You'll take good care of her, right?
Of course. You can count on me.
You just focus on your work.
Goodness, with that delicate face of yours,
who's taking care of whom? Forget it.
My hands and feet are perfectly fine.
You can work me as hard as you like.
It's for the best. It was only a matter of time.
- It's over. It's all over. - What's over?
What can he do?
Is he going to run off to the States again?
He convinced my daughter, who was doing just fine,
to make a movie with him.
He should see it through to the end.
I mean...
They have to make the movie together, sure.
What I'm saying is that Su Bin's feelings...
- are completely gone. - What feelings?
Love.
- Love. - Quit your nonsense and eat.
Yi Jae.
This is the irony of love.
A woman will stay with a man who makes her cry,
no matter what they tell her, right?
But a man can't stay with a woman he makes cry.
- Why? - Why? Because it's torture for him.
His heart is breaking. But a real man, you know?
He can't just sit there sobbing, can he?
- That's what it means to be a man. - Yeong Jae.
Joo Yeong Jae. Where did I go wrong raising you?
It's all thanks to you, Mom.
That wasn't a compliment.
Hi.
Do you still have the pins in your leg?
Hey. That's kind of a weird way to say good morning.
I searched about it. It said you probably had a plate put in.
I did. Just like the Iron Man.
Why didn't you get it taken out?
I couldn't get it removed. It's too close to a nerve,
so they said it would be risky to operate.
I see.
Does it still bother you sometimes? When is it the worst?
- Right now? - Now? Let me see.
Where?
Do you think you can figure out the problem just by looking at it?
I need to know what's going on.
It doesn't affect my daily life.
So it never hurts or anything?
Well, it throbs a little when it rains.
It hurts a little if I walk or run a lot,
especially at night.
Does massaging it help? Are you taking any medication?
Why are you writing that down? It's not bad enough for medication.
On a scale from 0 to 10, how would you rate the pain?
I don't know. It depends on my mood.
Then I'd better keep you in a good mood.
Just a second.
What about back then?
When you kissed me and ran away.
Joo Yi Jae, are you crazy? Forget it. Stop following me.
Joo Yi Jae, you'll get soaked.
It was a sleepless night for many reasons.
How? How much was it?
On a scale of 0 to 10?
- Just kidding. - Gosh.
So...
what can I do for you when it hurts?
Nothing. I just endure it.
I mean, how do you endure...
See you later.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
You've been uncomfortable, haven't you?
- No... - Excuse me for a moment.
- Gosh. -Why?
- I'll do it. Don't worry. - Gosh, you...
What? No.
Mister.
- What's all this? - Where should we install this?
- What's... - Oh, you're here. Come on in.
- Okay. - Joo Yi Jae, be careful.
- Hey, what is all this? - It's just something.
Be careful.
I was worried for nothing.
Go on, try it out. I looked up all the reviews for this.
This is supposed to be the best one.
(Gyeongseong Love Song)
I finally finished it.
Great job.
How did it feel to write again after so long?
You know, writing is...
like riding a bicycle.
Once you get the hang of it, you never forget.
Did I sound a little cocky just now?
I guess you forgot everything about pulling your hair.
No, I didn't.
I also know this is just the beginning.
Anyway, to celebrate finishing the first draft,
how about a drink? Deal?
Deal.
(President Song of Taebaek)
I'll get it out.
- I didn't know you had this. - I brought them.
It's like a trophy from my reporter days.
- You've won a lot of awards. - As I feel happy now,
you can pick what you want.
(President Song of Taebaek)
I want President Song of Taebaek.
Okay.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
It's good, right?
It's good, but it seems a little strong.
I really never imagined you becoming a reporter.
I didn't either. How many years was I a reporter?
I climbed a tree one day. A really old tree.
They said I couldn't have it, so I tried to steal it.
What's your best scene?
That arrogance of yours showing that this will probably do well too?
That just because I've gotten famous, or something...
That will never happen.
That's just because you're so cocky.
(Gyeongseong Love Song)
(Written and Directed by Woo Su Bin and Joo Yi Jae)
Gosh.
Director, this place looks completely different from before.
The studio is so nice.
For a housewarming gift for a place like this,
is toilet paper okay?
- Of course. - Billionaires use toilet paper.
Thank you. But where's the DP?
Hey, Director Woo.
(Director of Photography)
Director.
- It's been a while. - You've been well?
Do you still like gummies?
- My hands shake without these. - Oh my.
Thanks to the script you sent, the trip here wasn't boring.
I'm sorry. Are you still jet-lagged?
Well, I just came thinking of it as a vacation.
But on my way here, I realised...
I've been here before, about 20 years ago.
You shot Silent Waves here, don't you remember?
(Lighting Director)
You scared me.
Oh, you must be the lighting director.
Yes, that's right. I'm Kim Gwang Il, in charge of lighting.
It's Gwang for "light" and Il for "one."
Oh my, hello. I'm Shin Seok Gi, in charge of sound.
(Sound Recordist)
(Art Director)
- I'm Namgung Se Ra, Art Director. - Hello.
Thank you all so much for coming all this way. Really.
But where is Joo Yi Jae?
Oh, Director Joo Yi Jae is...
A staff meeting, all of a sudden?
I'm not mentally prepared for this yet.
Why is my GPS not functioning?
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
What do you want?
I was just going to ask for directions.
- Who asks directions these days? - Seriously.
Director Joo Yi Jae.
Who are you?
(Assistant Director)
I'm Ryu Sang Mok, the Assistant Director.
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. - That hurts...
- Are you okay? - That hurts. Really.
You grabbed me so suddenly, so I...
- You suddenly twisted it... - Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Please, this way. - That's right.
- Yes, hello everyone. - Welcome, AD.
The public parking lot is quite far, right?
Yes, I got completely lost.
I ran into Director Joo just outside.
Director Joo?
Hello. It's nice to meet you all.
- My name is Joo Yi Jae. - Well, at least I get to see you.
Good to see you.
Well, how about we save the introductions...
for after the location hunting?
- We have to go. - Location scouting. Now?
- Hurry up. We're busy. Let's go. - Let's go. Let's get going.
See you later, Director Joo.
Location scouting, right now?
Excuse me, just a moment.
Give me a second.
Just a moment, please.
Why?
Weren't we supposed to have a script meeting today?
Yes, we are. While I'm out scouting,
you can have the meeting with the producers.
Why am I not going?
Well, there are two directors.
It's better if we divide and conquer.
You said we'd do everything together.
If we're scouting the locations,
that means we'll definitely be hiking.
Don't tell me you're leaving me behind...
because you're worried my legs will hurt.
That's not it.
- I'll check out the sets too. - That's not what I meant.
Yi Jae,
I think this is for the best.
Let's just do it this way. Let's not talk about it anymore.
I'm going.
- Up ahead... - How many steps will we clock?
- Obvi. We'll easily pass 30,000. - What's "obvi?"
What?
- It means "obviously." - Jeez.
Gosh, my knees are killing me.
The people who aren't going are so lucky.
Right, Sang Mok?
Come on, but this location scouting...
is the highlight of pre-production, isn't it?
I'm honoured to be a part of it, Lighting Director.
- If hurt, don't be a burden. - That's a "burd."
Hey, why would you say something so hurtful, DP?
I feel sad to hear that.
Gwang Il's feelings are hurt.
Be safe.
Have a good meeting. And just in case...
Call me if anything comes up.
- Okay. - Don't worry.
- Have a safe trip. - Be safe.
Okay, the scene list is finalised. Next...
- Here. - Okay.
Okay, next I'll share the directing team's feedback.
Are you okay?
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
Oh, I'm fine.
I thought you died on the way.
I ordered ages ago, and it still says you're on your way.
Yes, the accident has been reported.
Since this will be processed as a customer refund,
the delivery fee will not be paid.
Are you okay? You're not badly hurt?
What about the repair costs?
If you don't have the money, I can lend you some.
(Grandma's Grilled Fish)
Gosh, it's salty.
Ma'am, this is what you mentioned last time.
So, the guy Ha Na was looking for...
and the guy from the shin-kicking incident...
- They are all the same guy? - Yes.
(Sim Yu Geon)
Interesting.
Should I get the grilled fish?
Ma'am, the soup was way too salty today.
Come on, ma'am.
You ate it all, so why the attitude now?
Hey.
(Nerve-racking Woman, Trembling Man)
You're really doing this?
I heard CEO Ahn is doting on Director Kim these days...
to cast you in that "nerve-racking woman" role.
Your mama's working so hard.
What's next? Is she going to bribe everyone with burgers?
This is so immature. It's making my ears bleed.
What does that have to do with you?
Of course it does have something to do with me.
I got dropped from this project because of you.
I was supposed to be the "trembling man."
But after the rumours about our fight got out,
- I became Oh Ha Na's ashtray. - But I don't smoke.
I was first in line, you know?
I had my meeting with the director ages ago.
We were all done with it.
If you got cut because of me, someone who hasn't read the script,
doesn't that say more about you?
What are you talking about? I heard you begged the director,
- and sent a handwritten letter. - What a joke.
See? This is all part of CEO Ahn's plan.
This is why you're just living in your own little paradise...
while there's a war zone out here.
Must be nice, right? Really nice.
The world must look so beautiful to you.
If you're that jealous, you can have it. I'm serious.
Have what? CEO Ahn?
- "Trembling man." It's yours. - What?
I'm not planning on staying here much longer.
I'm escaping.
What do you mean? Escaping?
Is skipping the wrap party your idea of an escape?
- Are you a fool? Get out. - Am I?
I'm taking this, okay? I'm really doing it.
You said you didn't want it, right? I'm taking it.
Don't you go back on your word.
I'm really doing it, okay?
Time for a group photo. Everyone, please gather around.
- Hurry up, come on. - Okay, let's get in position.
Let's take it quickly.
Gosh.
- Who are you looking for? - People in front, please sit down.
- Where is Yu Geon? - Here...
- Who's Yu Geon? - Please stand there...
- Please sit down quickly. - Gang Member three.
- Gang Member three? He died. - People in the back...
- Please come here. It'd be better. - When?
- On your day off. - Please...
So he's dead.
(The food of Simsim Seafood can be served through takeout or delivery.)
It's time you quit and come back home.
You've been at it long enough. Come home...
and learn the family business.
We haven't seen each other in two years.
Couldn't you at least ask how I've been or if I've eaten?
Am I asking you to take care of me when I'm sick?
Am I asking you for money?
I'm telling you to take this business.
I'm telling you, I don't want to.
And you think you enjoy being a delivery driver?
Whenever I see a motorcycle accident on the news,
my heart sinks.
Yu Geon, holding out like this...
isn't persistence. It's just stubbornness.
No.
I can do it.
I don't want to be left with a regret like your guitar, Dad.
Why did you come here?
Did you just come to upset me?
I just...
I came because I missed you, Dad.
But there's something I have to say before I go.
I...
I'm never going to quit. No, I can't quit.
I'm sorry, Dad.
That little punk.
(Open, Takeout Available)
You have one month.
If you don't come back,
I'll go to Seoul and drag you home myself.
You hear me?
(Open, Takeout Available)
You know your dad's just worried about you,
right?
He might not show it,
but he watches every single thing you're in.
I don't even know what you're in.
But he knows all the terms...
from close-ups to bust shots.
What good does that do?
All he ever does is tell me to come home.
Hey. Come on, you're Sim Yu Geon, Kaneshiro Takeshi of Saero High.
You're the face of our town. Why are you so discouraged?
Kaneshiro Takeshi? That's nonsense.
When I went to Seoul,
I saw guys better-looking than me are a dime a dozen.
Don't lie. Are you just teasing me because I've never been to Seoul?
Hey, I can speak in a Seoul accent too, you know.
Have you eaten?
Alright.
- Just focus on driving. - Have you eaten?
(Bunam Intercity Bus Terminal)
We're here. Get out.
Thanks.
Oh, right.
Hey, take this.
- What is it? - Your dad told me to give you this.
Hey, I'm taking off.
Hey, hey, Joo Yeong Jae.
(Bunam Intercity Bus Terminal)
- Hello? - Hello?
Is this Sim Yu Geon?
Yes, speaking.
Who's this?
It's me, Director Kang.
Gosh, this location manager is the worst.
I told him not to show the director this place,
and I was clear that we'd need at least ten PA.
Do you know how much money that'll cost?
Exactly. I'm sure they left it on the list on purpose.
Because they knew he'd approve it the moment he visits there.
They just didn't want to bother scouting other locations.
Those devious schemers.
Director Joo.
Could you please talk to him?
Pardon? Well, I...
- I'm not familiar with this. - What?
These location photos we're looking at...
(Gyeongseong Love Song Location Team)
Producer, she's not here.
I said she's not here.
What?
Are you not in this chat room?
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
- AD Sang Mok made this chat, right? - Yes.
I'll invite you right now. Gosh.
No, that's okay, Producer. It's just...
Director Woo might have done it...
because he didn't want to disturb my writing.
I'll get what I need from him directly.
That could be why.
I was spooked.
Seriously.
Why did he have to go there?
Director, we're heading out for the day.
Isn't the commute a hassle? If you don't mind,
- you're welcome to sleep here. - Oh, no, it's fine.
You should have a rest with no stress.
- Our place is really close by. - I live close by too, so...
- We'll get going then. - We'll get going.
- Oh, okay. - See you tomorrow.
- Good work today. - Good work.
- What's this? - Seriously?
- That's not funny at all. - Please stop...
with those kinds of jokes.
Director. We were going to our place, and we just stopped by...
Oh, yes.
- Could you have a seat? - Just a moment.
- Hello? - Yi Jae.
We're getting chicken. You in?
- I'm on my way now. - Where are you going? What?
- I have plans as well. - Oh, okay.
- What? You mean you'll join? - Just order it first.
You're supposed to order. Please order original fried chicken.
Did you order the chicken?
Chicken? Don't be ridiculous.
So you didn't order?
Seriously, why is she being like this again?
My legs...
Gosh.
- Hey, Gwang Il. - Yes?
Well, everyone. I know you're tired, but let's have a quick meeting.
Things can't go on like this.
Let's go.
(Munak Mountain)
These locations we've scouted over the past few days...
Are they really the best we can do?
I know it's not easy to shoot a period piece on this budget.
But I don't want to just shoot at some mediocre location and...
- try to fix it in post-production. - That's right.
Right.
- We have our pride to think about. - We have to do better.
We need to do more legwork.
Assistant Director, search the area around the set again.
No residents, no tourists, no power lines...
No power lines, no buildings in the shot,
and somewhere with good lighting. You know what I mean, right?
I get what you're saying, but you also said...
we can't use locations that are too recognizable.
If that's the case, a place like that doesn't exist.
No. Either it exists, or we haven't found it yet.
It's 1 of 2 things.
It's not that it doesn't exist.
- Let me see. - Director.
- You're here. - Please let me see...
I thought they were coming tomorrow.
The landowner suddenly didn't allow them to use the land.
So they wrapped things up and came.
- I see. - Okay.
It's too cramped, so it would be hard to film there.
Where did everyone go?
Back to their places. I sent them all away.
Why? Do you want to be alone?
- Should I go too? - Of course not.
I sent them because I want to be only with you.
How was the meeting?
Not bad.
Have a seat. You haven't seen the photos,
have you?
This place is perfect,
but we can't get cars in, so we dropped it.
And for this one, when we got there,
there wasn't enough space to work with.
So this one is the best option we have.
What do you think?
Are you really curious about my opinion?
- What? - Nod if you like it,
shake your head if you don't.
What should I do?
- I'll do whatever you say. - Why are you being like this?
Even the person who saw it in person can't make a decision.
Who am I to say if it's good or not?
I'm too ashamed to even face the crew...
who went through all that trouble.
I already spoke to them and arranged it...
What did you say to them?
That Joo Yi Jae is my first love,
that we have a special relationship, so I want to be considerate? Or...
That I wanted to exclude her from difficult tasks...
since her leg is bad now because of me
Why? Did someone say something to you?
No, no one has said anything. Don't you find that strange?
No one asks who I am, and how or why I'm here as a director.
Why do you think that is?
Yi Jae.
Joo Yi Jae.
What's wrong with me? Gosh.
I didn't even cry when I won the grand prize.
But why is this so sad?
But does something like this even sell these days?
- Ma'am. - Yes?
The car is waiting.
How do I look today, Director Kang?
- Did you just yawn? - Please.
Look again, carefully.
- Forget it. The contract. - You're... Yes, ma'am.
I feel fluttered because...
it's been a while since I had to go out and hustle.
- Let's move out. - Yes, ma'am.
(Top Line Entertainment)
- Let's go. - Yes, ma'am.
I think she's gone now.
Okay.
(Oh Ha Na)
(Exclusive Artist Contract)
(Gyeongseong Love Song)
Gyeongseong Love Song?
Wolhwajeong, where only a sliver of moonlight...
has settled.
In the middle of the darkness stands Nan Yeong.
Nan Yeong.
After catching her breath,
she sets down the heavy bag she's holding...
and takes something out.
In her trembling hands, she's holding dynamite.
She already made up her mind.
The moment she ignites this fuse...
(It will be aired on Friday, 10pm.)
will start everything.
Nan Yeong hides explosives all around Wolhwajeong,
then stands, gripping the fuse tightly.
Beneath the wall, Nan Yeong's face, illuminated by the flame of a match,
flickers with a red glow.
Tonight, Nan Yeong will explode Wolhwajeong.
I finally understand. The high walls of Wolhwajeong...
weren't a fence meant to protect me.
They were the bars of a cage that imprisoned me.
Now, I will smash it all with my own hands.
Let's go, Chae Yeon.
I found it. The way out.
Take your time.
Oh, it's fine.
I'm okay.
So,
have you made a decision?
I'm a little impatient.
Ma'am,
I want to be successful.
Within a month...
Is that possible?
I told you I'm impatient.
(Exclusive Artist Contract)
How are you feeling today?
I can't tell if this is real or if I'm dreaming.
But...
it's our first get-together,
but I guess our boss decided not to show up.
- He's filming a dating show today. - A dating show?
A dating show.
Seriously, what is he doing?
Well, whatever.
As long as I have the corporate card.
But he said you'd be paying for it.
- Me? - He said to keep the receipt.
Is he trying to make me go broke?
Oh, Director Joo.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Let's drink.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Hey, Gwang Il. I heard Director Seo is filming...
on Yulgokdo Island right now. Isn't that place close to here?
You're thinking of going? Gosh, don't even think about it.
I heard it's total chaos over there.
One wrong move and your name will end up...
in the credits for that film, DP.
Yes, I heard it's a total boot camp over there.
The crew is ready to build a raft...
to get out of there. It's absolute chaos.
You're talking about Director Seo Dong Yoon, right?
He's famous for being incredibly demanding, isn't he?
I hear it's one of the toughest sets to be on.
That's the rumour going around.
Director Joo.
Are you a bit soft, Director Joo?
A director is supposed to be demanding.
That's why Director Seo is where he is today.
That's why the crew members who survive his sets...
wear it like a badge of honour.
Exactly. It's a point of pride for them.
Oh, there you are, Art Director.
Why are you sitting all the way over here in the corner?
Art Director, you went to Seonghwa University, right?
So you're my senior from school. Should I call you Namgung?
Just call me Se Ra.
Yes, Se Ra.
I'm Ryu Sang Mok.
Theater and Film major, class of 2006, Seonghwa University.
I don't have much school spirit.
Then maybe you'll take a liking to me?
- Hey there. - Wait, who are you talking to?
Drink up, drink up.
Drink up.
Cheers.
And what about Director Joo?
- Yes? - Which university...
did you graduate from?
I mean, why'd you become a reporter instead of using your major?
I was...
Hey, cheers, everyone.
- Drink up. - Beer, beer, beer.
- Here you go. - Cheers.
Please give me one more...
Life's so unfair, isn't it?
Tell me about it.
Someone works himself to the bone in this industry for 13 years.
Yet, he doesn't have his own work.
Hey, Five-Year.
That's a very specific number.
Are you talking about me?
I'm just saying...
With all these legendary veterans still in the game,
some nobody...
- Right? - True.
That's what I'm saying.
What a life.
I have to pee.
- This can't be right, can it? - You're right.
Okay, she's a former reporter.
Fine, I'll give her that.
But she's never even studied film.
But there are plenty of directors who didn't major in film, you know?
Hey.
There's a big difference between them and her.
It's not like she went to some top-tier schools.
Just some grad from a no-name university...
waltzes in here, not knowing her place.
Hey, what the heck? Why isn't anyone coming out?
- You'll be in there all day? - No, no, stop.
- Should I just kick it down? - You shouldn't do that.
Hey, no, don't.
Hey, come on. You're too drunk.
Why are you crying?
- What's wrong with you? - I'm not crying.
Do you own the toilet? Get out now.
- Just a minute. - Hey. Get out.
- No. - Hey.
- Hey, hey, hey. - Do you even know who I am?
- Hey. You really have to pee. - You little punk.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - What...
Director.
What the...
(Restroom)
Hey.
Seriously, what are we going to do? Gosh.
I just said the truth...
- about her educational background. - Yi Jae.
- Hey, man. Hey. - Restroom? Someone was in there.
Please keep it down.
I'm talking loudly so she can hear me, right?
How is it possible? I'm the one who majored in it, and she's not.
- Please, man, please. - I want to be a director.
What's wrong with you?
This is my first time, so...
Honestly, it's true. I'll need a lot of your help.
- Of course. - I'm counting on you all.
We look forward to working with you.
I think I'm drunk...
Have you tried this? It's really delicious.
- Director Woo. Come have a drink. - Let's drink together.
- Have a drink. - Come over here.
Great, great.
- Now that our director's here. - Cheers.
- This too. - It's delicious?
It's really good.
You should've called me.
I should've at least called...
Producer, I'm going to head out now.
Are you heading home? Do you need a ride?
- No, I already called a cab. - Okay, get home safe.
- Thank you. - Get home safe.
- Well then... - Where are you going?
- Hey, man. Hey. - Let's go for a second round.
- Hey. - Let's go for a second round.
- No, no. - Let's go for a second round.
- No. - Let's go for a second round.
(A Lavish Feast)
Hello, Director.
- When did you get here? - Assistant Director.
Yes.
This will be the first and last time that I explain my decisions.
Pardon?
What are you... What are you trying to say...
Yi Jae wrote "Gyeongseong Love Song..."
when she was a senior in high school.
That's why I'm letting Yi Jae handle all the script meetings.
I decided it would be more efficient for me...
to handle the location hunting in the meantime.
- Oh, right. - Assistant Director.
Director Joo Yi Jae is doing her job perfectly.
- Yes, she is. - Does this make you uncomfortable?
No, Director.
Oh, no. That's not it at all.
I'm sorry.
You don't owe me an apology.
From now on, let's all...
just do our own part...
while respecting one another.
- Yes. - Enjoy your meal.
(A Lavish Feast)
You're back?
- Ma'am. - Yes?
Please put the staff's meal on my tab.
You're paying for everyone?
My goodness.
No, no one has said anything.
Don't you find that strange?
No one asks who I am,
and how or why I'm here as a director.
I just said the truth about her educational background.
- Hey, man. Hey. - It's...
Please keep it down.
I'm talking loudly so she can hear me, right?
I'm the one who majored in it...
- Hello? - Where are you? We need to talk.
I'm right in front of your place.
(Jaejae Noodles)
What are you doing?
Just watch.
- Why are you running? - Just stay there and watch.
See? I can run like this, and I'm perfectly fine.
It doesn't hurt at all.
You know...
You know what my life has been like.
I've spent entire days stuck in mudflats,
and climbed countless mountains.
So please, stop it.
Because of you, I feel my scars...
are becoming obvious.
If you really feel sorry for me,
if you pity me so much,
then please recognise that I'm here now...
despite everything that happened.
And please understand what I was feeling...
when I finally made it here.
I really want to do a good job.
I don't want to have any more regrets.
So help me, Woo Su Bin.
So I can start running again.
What's your dream?
To be a film director.
Hurry up, come on.
So? Pretty cool, right?
I, Joo Yi Jae, will become a humane film director.
Go, Joo Yi Jae.
Let's make movies together.
Let's do something great together.
A romance.
Let's write a romance together. We'll write an amazing romance plot.
I admired you so much.
This bright, shining face of yours.
That's why I like you.
Yi Jae.
This is something I should have done...
when we were 19.
I'll stop...
here.
So you can shine brighter.
I never thought that my feelings for you...
would become a burden to you.
I'm sorry.
No.
No, I wasn't asking for an apology.
I was just asking you to help me.
I'm sorry...
that this is the best I can do.
Anyway...
What's important is that we finish the movie together.
Still...
Give me some time to sort out my feelings.
Then until the revised script is ready,
I'll work from home.
Take care.
What?
Why does that sound like a final goodbye?
It is a final goodbye.
To my first love.
When the revised script is ready, let's meet as colleagues.
Oh, so that's how it is?
Yes.
Well then...
Goodbye, Yi Jae.
Yes.
See you soon,
Director Joo.
I'm going.
(Dream To You)
Director Joo Yi Jae.
I really want to be in that movie.
- Is someone else coming? - Sim Yu Geon.
- Su Bin. - What do you think you're doing?
Are you casting Sim Yu Geon or dropping Joo Yi Jae?
It's uncomfortable and unpleasant when you show up unannounced.
It's creating so much buzz. The moment the Catfish entered,
the entire vibe changed.
Why does it feel like it went by in a flash?
The time I waited for you was longer...
Well, I'll be on my way.
Then what were we? What were we back then?
I think it was love.